ah ah hun doubt we're not even positive
that today is my actual birthday well
it's been three full moons since Myron
found that old calendar with the two
weeks crossed off after Christmas with
one of those cheap red pens I really
might last for like 40 50 good cross out
so I just don't want to make this into a
big thing you know if we just keep on
working on come on Gary I thought we
talked to him about this we did talk to
him about this 97 broadcast do you mind
I'm sector 7b 8r you're interrupting our
music why are you bothering me what have
I told you morons I don't broadcast
coordinates every hour every single hour
on the hour the fate of every living
creature is gonna be compromised hello
uh that gives me an idea Gary could you
maybe shut out Charlie's birthday sure I
guess wait I don't want to do that great
um just say that we're gonna have a
party over by where those two guys kill
each other at sundown NAT stop it and
it's byob or BYO everything excuse us
hey I don't want to do this well we
gotta do something we are not doing
anything it's not our birthday well yeah
it is or wait what listen I think I want
a little space okay that's what I want
for my birthday well what am I supposed
to do do whatever you want
you want to know what I wish for one
more wishes
excuse me hi what's the mocha tsunami
it's a low acidity blend from Yemen it's
got a little bit of truth to it for the
only place in the city that has it right
now it's the Yemeni dry season obviously
why do you want it is it coffee are you
are you serious I hate this place
Charlie
a quick question about your 433 bumped
out to Friday I've been back and forth
with these guys all week trying to find
a spot for this thing and I'm like ah
who is this kind of a queen of sheba and
it turns out yes it is actually the
Queen Sheba which is apparently a place
again and requires a sovereign monarch
to govern it so long story short we're
looking at that on Friday now so you're
clear for 30 okay 01 yeah what you need
a snack there's egg salad in all of your
drawers I felt them today no no
excellent it's just uh it's my birthday
or uh was my birthday uh we can go 10 10
days ago Amy Wow uh yes I knew that of
course anything I'll organize something
an oversized car and oversized cake it
works or um if I'm free at four thirty
maybe we could all duck out um together
everybody and we could like Oh a little
party uh yeah sure uh you know what I I
think our d is pretty swamped today so
we'll just push that to Monday oh love
you love you too
why am I responsible for Mickey I'm not
responsible for making you're not
responsible and you know that when she
was on something it builds and builds
ability that never comes out so like
suddenly it's like there's an explosion
of anger I've broken many things Nikki
was bisexual yes he was by which i'm
sorry i don't know i don't know that's
that's what I'm saying that's what I'm
saying he was it and i'm a very sexual
person I've always been a very special
person it's like I'm very open minded
I'm in an open relationship with caramel
and to not miss Nikki's hurry uh-huh I
do not miss him he was truly a monster
he was among horrible Nina to LA no it's
like a crushed by a rock so eun's yeah
that rock Wow hello is anyone in there I
uh I got porcupine needles in all my
hands I didn't even grab it but it was
running and uh oh wow guys know ah man
okay anyway um why didn't you help him
oh no we're not opening that door not
for anyone but you have a first aid kit
right there that's art yeah and it's
site-specific so we would have to
contact the artist which you I can't
even imagine the legality where you
going I've plans with a friend actually
so I'm just gonna I'll see
I bet his vaniqa oh he's obsessed with
her oh wow Oh God thank you oh God thank
God thank God thank you guys thank you
guys oh I can't hmm I sorry I can't I
haven't talked to a human a human a new
door there was a door don't worry um I
just being kind bars hi hello hi all
right hi i'm matt conner I think it's
connor journey I thought it was I feel
like it was a symbol it was one syllable
but I also feel like it was Connor ok
we're going i'm still time yeah charlie
hey where have you been I'm just kind of
wandering around um this is Connor how
was your birthday it's fine aight a
really stale scone huh honestly I'm just
glad to be back here even if it is just
us yeah Austin Connor hello oh sorry was
that that is too loud am i speaking too
loudly loudly hey guys hey hey guys what
are you doing here there's something on
the radio we in the right place I think
so James hey yo hey oh hi Jerry hey guys
oh my god thanks so much for coming so
what do you want to do Charlie it's your
party well it's our party now we can go
wherever we want do whatever we want
it's just us
right well
we're two guys
wait is this a party yeah it's a party
for Charlie you know you know what I'm
gonna close i hate this medication balls
yeah sorry you still have those yeah
sorry
ah still no don't
you